♪ 无心过问你的心里 ♪
♪ 我的吻已厌倦 ♪
♪ 我的亏欠 ♪
♪ 代替你所爱的人 ♪
♪ 这个时候我习落花一样飘落下来的是我的视线 ♪
失去了色彩
♪ 飞到远方 ♪
♪ 还好你说的还好 ♪
♪ 我没忘 ♪
♪ 岁月把荒唐谱成了乐章 ♪
♪ 每一首都荡气回肠 ♪
♪ 飞到远方 ♪
飞到远方
♪ 回忆的热汤就留给回忆去唱 ♪
♪ 愿我从此自由开阔 ♪
♪ 你也从此别来无恙 ♪
♪ And i won't go ♪
♪ Cause i believe it ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ I believe i've got something ♪
♪ So oh let me tell you something true ♪
♪ The rythons of your heart ♪
♪ Connect to me in the way that i don't understand i need your hand ♪
♪ The rivers of your heart ♪
♪ I wanna swim inside ♪
♪ I know ♪
♪ It's kind of strange ♪
♪ It's never sa ♪
♪ I wanna be forever ♪
♪ And you ♪
♪ You forever ♪
♪ Closed off from lei ♪
♪ Didn't need the pin once or twice was enough ♪
♪ And it was all in vin times ♪
♪ Stars to pass before you know it ♪
♪ You're frozen ♪
♪ But something happened for the very first time with you ♪
♪ My heart melted to the ground found something true ♪
♪ And everyone looking around thinking ♪
♪ I'm going crazy hbut ♪
♪ I don't care what they say ♪
♪ I'm in love with you to try to pull me away ♪
♪ But they don't know the truth ♪
♪ My heart is crippled by event that i keep on closing ♪
♪ You cut me open ♪
♪ And i keep beating ♪
♪ Keep keep beating love ♪
♪ Keep beating ♪
♪ Keep bleeding ♪
♪ Keep keep bleeding love ♪
♪ You cut me open ♪
♪ And i ♪
♪ I get so waking the knees ♪
♪ I can hardly speak ♪
♪ I lose conttrue and something takes ♪
♪ So over me in the days ♪
♪ Your love so amazing is not a fa ♪
♪ I want you to stay with me by my side ♪
♪ I will love out of my pride ♪
♪ Your love is so sweet ♪
♪ And knocks me right off my feet ♪
♪ Can't explain why your love and makes me weak ♪
Yeah